https://www.justbewell.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy | JustBeWell.com
Call us today!
hypnotherapy & nlp
making lives better
SEARCH:
HomeProductsTestimonialsTeamHypnotherapy & NLP BlogCartPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy/Privacy PolicyBook An Appointment »Or visit our online shop » Home  > Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how JustBeWell.com uses and protects any information that you give JustBeWell.com when you use this website.
JustBeWell.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
JustBeWell.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
This policy is effective from: July 2016What we collectWe may collect the following information:• name• contact information including email address• demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests• other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersWhat we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:• Internal record keeping.• We may use the information to improve our products and services• We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.• From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.What is a cookie?
Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise a user’s device.You can find more information about cookies at:• www.allaboutcookies.org• www.youronlinechoices.eu• For a video about cookies visit a look at cookies
Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improve the user experience. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests. The cookies used on this website have been categorised based on the categories found in the ICC UK Cookie guide.Category 1: strictly necessary cookies
These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies services you have asked for, like shopping baskets or e-billing, cannot be provided.Category 2: performance cookies
These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.
By using our website, you agree that we can place these type of cookies on your device.Category 3: functionality cookies
These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. For instance, a website may be able to provide you with local weather reports or traffic news by storing in a cookie the region in which you are currently located. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.
By using our website, you agree that we can place these type of cookies on your device.Category 4: targeting cookies or advertising cookiesThese cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organizations.A list of all the cookies used on this website by category is set out below.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:• whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes• if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at JustBeWell.com adminWe will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.A small fee will be payable.If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to: 14 Grove Crescent Gloucester GL4 4JJIf you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.Please feel free to make comments and or ask questions.Comments are closed.HYPNOTHERAPY RECORDINGSHelp YourselfGet this and many other recordings from our online shopVisit The Shop »TestimonialsSuccess StoriesThere are scores of testimonials that pay tribute to our success in helping people make changes....Read Success Stories »OTHER ISSUESWe can help withPrivacy PolicyAddictions TreatmentAddictions TreatmentTestimonialsTestimonialsTestimonialsTestimonialsHypertension HelpPMS - PMTShy Bladder Syndrome - ParuresisDizzinessObsessive ThoughtsTestimonialsTinnitus
Book an appointment »Or visit the shop online » Find a specialistUKLondonSteve TromansMondays and TuesdaysT: 07900 240192Email & Biog »BirminghamDebbie WilliamsT: 0121 241 0728Email & Biog »BucksPaul WrightT: 07768 877719Email & Biog »LeedsNick KempT: 01274 622 994Email & Biog »ManchesterNick KempT: 01274 622 994Email & Biog »SurreyTina TaylorT: 07946 351640Email & Biog »ScotlandCarol RobertsonEdinburgh, Glasgow and
throughout ScotlandT: 0131 440 2589Email & Biog »IrelandKaren SlatteryT: 087 3315 568T: 087 2860 269Email & Biog »International OnlineEnglish Speaking OnlyGina PickersgillM: 07932 958 262Email & Biog »CanadaVancouverHarry NicholsT: 604-421-1722Email & Biog »   Kathy Welter-NicholsT: 604-421-1722Email & Biog » Toronto, OntarioElizabeth Payea-ButlerT: 416-720-2151Email & Biog »USANew York CityDoug O'BrienT: 718-768-4098Email & Biog »Chicago, IllinoisBarbara SteppT: 708-799-5329Email & Biog »Portland, OregonJim KelleyT: 503-756-4148 Email & Biog » Los AngelesPam CastilloT: 818-654-9660Email & Biog »AustraliaNetherlandsItaliaSydneyEnas SaadT: 0439 854 562Email & Biog »PerthBeverley de la HarpeT: 0412 777 111Email & Biog »MelbourneAdam SzmerlingT: 03 9557 9113Email & Biog »AlmereRik van BastelaarT: +31 (0)36 880 74 68M: +31 (0)6 487 348 55Email & Biog »  Reggio EmiliaAlessandro MoraT: +39 0522 337611Email & Biog »  Other resources worldwideCanada Hypnotherapy And NLP Vancouver Toronto »Ireland Hypnotherapy And NLP: Ireland »©2020 JustBeWell.com
This site uses cookies: Find out more.Okay, thank you
